<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jonathan</title>
    <link>https://lowj.github.io/tags/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jonathan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>You</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lowj.github.io/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thinkpad Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://lowj.github.io/posts/tp_kb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lowj.github.io/posts/tp_kb/</guid>
      <description>tp-keyboard ! The goal of this project is to make a useable desktop keyboard from the keyboard of the ThinkPad L420 laptop and making the trackpoint functional.
I originally started this project back in early 2020 where I spent alot of time decoding the Keyboard matrix and figuring out the pinout of the trackpoint module. I created a breakout board to easily access the pins of the keyboards FFC cable which made it easier to work with while decoding the matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macbook Lightbar</title>
      <link>https://lowj.github.io/posts/lightbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lowj.github.io/posts/lightbar/</guid>
      <description>After 7 years my Early 2015 Macbook’s battery was barely working and on its last legs. After getting a new battery from iFixit I opened my MacBook and replaced it. I booted it up and noticed there was a bunch of smudges / damage on the screen. I realized that some of the alcohol I used during the installation process sept through the keyboard and got onto the screen and caused damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micromouse</title>
      <link>https://lowj.github.io/posts/micromouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lowj.github.io/posts/micromouse/</guid>
      <description>[TODO] https://github.com/micromouseuci/micromouse-kit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LazyBoardV2 - Macropad w/ RGB OLED</title>
      <link>https://lowj.github.io/posts/lazy-boardv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lowj.github.io/posts/lazy-boardv2/</guid>
      <description>Macropad featuring 12 hotswappable switches, a RGB OLED screen, and RGB for each key. Firmware written by my friend William
Hardware: MCU - Teensy 4.0
RGB OLED - SPI
WS2812B RGB LEDs
The board uses a daughter board to attach the RGB LEDs.
Buttons and DIP switches in the back allow for USER profiles to be programmed in.
Case: 3D printed PLA case. Consists of the main case to mount the PCB, plate to mount switches, and a shield for the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
